Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
I'm calm, steady.
I slept well. 8.2 hours.
No bad dreams.
I am ready to go.
Ready to do my job
to the best of my abilities.
I am focused
only on the essential,
to the exclusion of all else.
I will make
only pragmatic decisions.
I will not allow myself
to be distracted.
I will not allow
my mind to linger
on that which is unimportant.
(KEYS CLATTER)
I will not rely
on anyone or anything.
I will not be
vulnerable to mistakes.
Resting BPM, 47. Submit.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Your psychological evaluation
has been approved.
As a reminder,
please perform any safety
and equipment checks...
ROY: I always wanted
to become an astronaut...
for the future
of mankind and all.
At least, that's what
I always told myself.
I see myself from the outside.
Smile, present a side.
It's a performance...
with my eye on the exit.
Always on the exit.
Just don't touch me.
(INAUDIBLE)
MAN 1: (ON RADIO)
Take care, Major. Be careful.
ROY: Thanks for that.
(DOOR HISSES)
(DOOR OPENS)
MAN 2: (ON RADIO)
Roy, Bravo post
has got a robotic arm
on 93 Echo...
appears to be malfunctioning.
We're gonna need you to take
a team down there
and check it out.
Run some diagnostics. Over.
ROY: Copy that.
Heading that way.
DOUG: (ON RADIO) Good morning
to our astronauts up there
on the International
Space Antenna.
Sure is a beautiful day.
Just perfect
to try and contact...
our distant neighbors
out there in the heavens.
ROY: At least
it's comfortable out here.
DOUG: I got some scores here.
Let's see, it was Iowa State
over Kansas, 35 - 16.
ROY: Space I understand.
Control, I have visual
on the arm. Over.
OFFICER 1: Affirmative, Major.
Proceed.
ROY: Copy that.
Moving to the unit now.
- (ELECTRICAL HUMMING)
- (HEAVY THUD)
(ELECTRICAL PULSATING)
(PULSATING STOPS)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
Control, I'm seeing
a power surge on C-post.
You getting that?
OFFICER 2: Uh...
Roger that, Roy...
ROY: Control, we got a lot
of people up there. Over.
ASTRONAUT: Control. Control,
I think we have some spikes...
OFFICER 2: Please just stand
by, we're working the issue.
Just stand by.
ASTRONAUT: Control,
they're happening everywhere.
(ASTRONAUT YELLS)
(SCREAMING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(RADIO CHATTER
CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
ROY: Command, cutting power.
OFFICER 2:
Get off the tower now!
(PEOPLE CONTINUE SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
You've gotta bail out!
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
ASTRONAUT: Oh, my God!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING ON RADIO)
ROY: Control, McBride.
I'm in a spin.
Atmosphere's too thin
to stabilize.
I'm trying to keep
the tumble down,
so I don't black out.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
Control, do you read?
(PANTING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PANTING)
(RUSTLING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
ROY:
"A self-destructive side."
That's what
she used to say to me.
(RAIN PATTERING)
I should feel something.
I survived.
REPORTER: In what has become
known as "The Surge"...
a series of destructive
electrical storms
has wreaked havoc
across the globe...
and scientists are concerned
we've not seen
the last of them yet.
Their origin? Outer space.
The cause? Unknown so far...
(BEEPS)
COMMANDER: This is a message
from SPACECOM.
In light of
the recent catastrophe...
your attendance
is required for a debrief...
to be held in Building 91,
Vandersteen Base.
Please note, this meeting will
be classified "top secret."
Roy, how are you? Thanks for coming in.
Appreciate it.
ROY: General.
This is Lieutenant
General Rivas, Director of
- U.S. SPACECOM Special Ops.
- Hi.
- Sir.
- RIVAS: Major.
STROUD: Adjutant General
Vogel, head of Security.
- Major.
- Ma'am.
STROUD: They flew
all the way in from Virginia
just last night,
just to see you.
Well, thank you.
Your, uh, profile
is certainly very impressive.
You've done exceptionally well
on all the assessment tests.
Basic combat,
space training.
Just exceptional
across the board.
The rumor is that
your pulse rate
has never gone above 80...
in any of the spacewalks,
skywalks,
and even on
this most recent fall.
Is that correct?
Well, so far, sir.
STROUD:
That's very impressive.
According to this,
married once, no children?
Yes, sir.
It's dangerous business,
as we know.
Best not to
subject others to it.
Fair enough.
Well, we didn't
bring you in here
to talk about
your fall, Roy.
We have something...
of a highly classified nature
to show you.
Please have a seat, Major.
Yes, ma'am.
RIVAS: What you are
about to see are
spectrogram images of Neptune.
These are cosmic ray bursts.
That was taken
just 11 days ago.
It released
high-energy particles...
that caused
a catastrophic power surge
all over the world.
And that's what
almost killed you.
The rays grow stronger
as they radiate towards us
here on Earth.
Major, what can you tell us
about the Lima Project?
First manned expedition to
the outer solar system, sir.
(DEVICE HUMS)
Some 29 years ago,
as you know.
RIVAS:
And the commander was...
He was my father, sir.
The ship disappeared
approximately 16 years
into the mission.
No data was ever recovered.
Deep space missions
were halted after that.
Yes, that's him.
Can you tell us how you
handled your father's absence?
Well...
My mother was
certainly distressed by it.
Uh, she was quite ill
at the time.
But he was,
uh, committed to his job...
and I'm sure it was very
difficult for him as well.
STROUD: Roy...
we have something that might
come as quite a shock to you.
We believe your father
is still alive near Neptune.
Where exactly,
we do not know.
Now, we've sent out
numerous drones,
but obviously,
it's a vast area to cover.
My father's alive, sir?
We believe so.
STROUD: Roy, The Surge
seems to be the result
of some kind
of anti-matter reaction.
Now, the Lima Project was
powered by that material...
and your father
was in charge of it.
Now, we're talking about
a potentially unstoppable
chain reaction here.
The uncontrolled release
of anti-matter...
could ultimately threaten
the stability of
our entire solar system.
All life could be destroyed.
Major, we would
like you to send
a personal message on Mars
by secure laser...
to what we hope
is the Lima Project.
The text of your message
would be prepared in advance,
of course.
Mars, sir?
I'm going to Mars?
It is the last secure hub
we have.
STROUD: Roy,
we need to find out
just what
we're up against here.
Our underground Mars base
was the only one
unaffected by The Surge.
And we believe
a personal plea,
from you to your father,
might elicit a response.
We can track that signal...
locate him and figure out
a way to stop this.
What is happening out there is
a crisis of unknown magnitude.
Now, we're counting on you
to help us find him.
Are you with us?
- Yes, I am, sir.
- STROUD: Good.
You deploy first
to the moon.
Our long-range rockets
are stationed there
on the Far Side.
Everything after that will be
on a need-to-know basis.
Yes, sir.
Given the magnitude
of the threat...
a cover story is being
formulated to avoid all panic.
You'll be traveling
commercially to the moon
to keep a low profile.
Colonel Pruitt will be your
point person from here on.
Absolute top secrecy
must be maintained.
ROY: "Are you with us?"
Like I have a choice.
My dad was a pioneer.
He sacrificed himself for the
search for intelligent life.
My dad was the program.
I was 16 when he left,
29 when he disappeared.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Archived
message, received 27 years...
- 3 months, 2 days ago.
- ROY: And that's that.
CLIFFORD: Roy, this is
a message from your father.
I'm coming at you
from the Lima Project.
Just on our way past Jupiter
and ultimately on to Neptune.
I know you have seen
that we have excited
real and enormous interest...
around the world,
and we are grateful for it.
We're doing big things
up here, real big.
Namely, we're about to answer
the number one question...
when do we find all the
intelligent life out there?
And we know we will.
We're going to the edge
of the heliosphere...
where the sun's
magnetic field
won't affect
our instruments one bit.
We'll be able to examine any
star system for complex life.
Never been done before,
and we sure are optimistic.
I feel your energy back home,
and of course, I think of God.
I'm overwhelmed at seeing
and feeling His presence...
so close.
I love you, my son.
MAN: Hello, Roy.
I'm here to go
on this trip with you.
Keep my eye on ya.
Colonel Pruitt,
good to meet you.
Actually...
we've met.
It was a long time ago.
I knew your dad.
We were close,
he and I.
We started out together,
went to Purdue together.
He was a brilliant man.
- I know.
- Yeah.
And I remember going
to the house and seeing you.
You were running around
everywhere.
You drove your
poor mother nuts, but...
How do you feel?
Is this part
of my psych eval?
(CHUCKLES) Uh...
No, not really, but yes.
I mean, you're going
to be monitored constantly...
your mental state,
your emotional state.
You have a direct connection
with the subject.
Colonel, for what it's worth,
I think my father's dead.
(SIGHS)
Yeah, um...
I was a lunar astronaut
for SPACECOM for 31 years.
And I came to the
realization out there...
a voyage of exploration
can be used
for something
as simple as escape.
I'm telling you this, Roy,
because we have to
hold out the possibility...
that your father
may be hiding from us.
Do you think
you're ready to go?
I'm ready.
All right.
AUTOMATED VOICE: (ON SPEAKERS)
Your pre-launch quarantine
is almost complete.
You have shown no evidence
of bacterial
or viral infection...
ROY: So many times in my life,
I've screwed up.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Although
all efforts have been made...
ROY: I've talked,
when I should have listened.
I've been harsh,
when I should have
been tender.
AUTOMATED VOICE: In the event
of illness or accident...
please make certain
that you have listed
any family members...
spouse, or significant other
as your next of kin,
in your personal file.
Volume down.
Message.
Personal directory. Eve.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
Hi, Eve, it's Roy.
Uh...
I'm away again,
no surprise there.
I just wanted to say...
I made a promise
to always be truthful.
But I wasn't.
Listen, I wanted to say...
I didn't want you to go.
Delete.
Cancel.
(COMPUTER BUZZES)
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
(ON SPEAKERS) Good morning.
ROY: I've been trained
to compartmentalize.
SPACECOM requires you
to complete
a pre-launch
psychological evaluation.
ROY: It seems to me
that's how I approach my life.
Resting BPM is 56.
Didn't sleep much last night,
but it shouldn't be a problem.
I remain mission ready.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
You have been approved
for lunar travel.
WOMAN: Is it your first time
to the moon?
ROY: No,
but it's been a while.
WOMAN: Are you planning
on traveling outside
the secure zone
on your visit?
ROY: No.
WOMAN: Again.
- How's that?
- ROY: Okay.
- WOMAN: Okay, not too snug?
- Yeah, it feels all right.
WOMAN: Breathe.
ANNOUNCER: (ON PA)
Virgin flight 6092,
to Tycho Base, Moon,
boarding now.
(HYDRAULICS HISSING)
Welcome aboard, sir.
- I'm Captain Lu.
- Thank you.
- Hi, Captain.
- Watch the step.
- Duck your head.
- Okay.
- Hello, welcome. Flight pack?
- Hello.
- Yes, thanks.
- Great.
- Third seat, to your right.
- Okay.
Excuse me.
- Hello.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(ENGINES ROARING)
CAPTAIN LU: (ON PA)
We remind you,
the moon is borderless.
Many mining zones
are disputed territory
and considered to be
in a state of war.
Please stay within
the restricted, safe area...
Excuse me?
May I have a blanket
and pillow pack please?
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Sure. $125.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Payment accepted.
- Thank you.
CAPTAIN LU:
As we approach,
some of you can see
the grand telescope array...
near the Atlas crater.
It's the moon's
largest facility
for extraterrestrial research.
FLIGHT ATTENDANT: Hot towel?
- Oh, thank you.
- Thank you for flying with us.
We do appreciate it.
CAPTAIN LU:
Please prepare for landing.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ROY: All the hopes we ever
had for space travel...
covered up by drink stands
and T-shirt vendors.
Just a recreation of what
we're running from on Earth.
We are world-eaters.
If my dad could
see this now...
he'd tear it all down.
(MAN ANNOUNCING
INDISTINCTLY ON PA)
PRUITT: Our rocket
is named Cepheus.
The crew will be
SPACECOM military personnel.
They're completely unaware
of our mission.
We have to
keep it that way.
The launchpad is on the
other side of no man's land.
It's very dangerous...
so we'll have armed personnel
to protect us and escort us
to the Far Side.
Colonel, can I ask
what the last conversation
you had with my dad was?
It was not very pleasant.
We quarreled about
my leaving the program.
He accused me
of being a traitor.
And if you were
to find him...
then what?
Is this very difficult
for you, son?
This being about your father?
No.
No, my dad's a hero.
SPACECOM's trying
to impugn a man
who's given his entire life
to the program.
I think it's despicable.
Or desperate at best.
(COMPUTER CHIMES)
ANNOUNCER: (ON PA)
We are approaching Terminal R,
lunar rover hangar.
We've been having trouble
with pirates since September.
Some countries have been
giving them safe haven.
They'll take hostages
or go for our rovers.
It's like the Wild West
out there...
but we'll get you
to your spacecraft.
This your first time
in a war zone?
Three years over
the Arctic Circle.
LEVANT: All right.
And a heck of a lot
of Army-Navy games.
(CHUCKLES) Well,
I guess there's not much
you haven't seen, right?
Well, look,
it's almost a full moon.
A large stretch of the
Far Side's real black,
so let's suit up.
ANNOUNCER: (ON PA)
Lunar Rovers, Group C,
set for departure...
to the Far Side launch complex
through gate 12.
Please maintain
situational awareness.
COMMAND PERSONNEL: (ON RADIO)
Rover 7, confirming settings.
LEVANT: Bearing two-niner-oh.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(ON RADIO) Roy?
Yes, Colonel.
PRUITT: Look at it.
The big blue marble.
Never ceases to amaze me.
ROY: Lieutenant,
you clocking this?
MAN: Yeah, same here.
I can't ID any
national markings. Over.
- ROY: Lieutenant...
- MAN 2: At 7 o'clock...
LEVANT: Alpha,
what do we got here?
Alpha, we have
what looks like
unidentified rovers
approaching our position.
Possible pirate activity,
and I got a couple
of VIPs with me.
MAN: Roger,
moving to flank you.
Uh, Alpha, we may need
some ballistics help up here.
Potential hostile situation...
ROY: Here we go again,
fighting over resources.
MAN 3: We got two coming up
on our rear, 7 o'clock.
WOMAN 1:
Appears to be pirates,
possibly looking
for valuables.
We'll send
ballistic support ASAP.
ROY: What the hell
am I doing here?
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
ROY: Shit!
LEVANT: Alpha,
we need backup ASAP!
We're being ambushed!
- MAN: Mayday, mayday, mayday!
- ROY: Give me a weapon!
LEVANT: Just hold on!
ROY: LRV-3 down.
(PEOPLE YELLING)
LRV-2 down.
(AIR HISSING)
LEVANT: Alpha,
we're gonna go off path
to reach the Far Side.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
ROY: I have a puncture!
- PRUITT: Roy!
- I have a puncture.
(AIR CONTINUE HISSING)
LEVANT: Roy, you all right?
ROY: I'm okay.
LEVANT: Alpha, repeat,
we need...
PRUITT: Lieutenant!
Oh, Lord!
(PANICKED CHATTER)
COMMAND PERSONNEL: Go, go, go.
Hey, break it up.
ROY: We are not clear.
I repeat, we are not clear.
We have multiple
enemy craft in pursuit.
PRUITT: Roy!
They're trying to ram us!
(ROY BREATHING HEAVILY)
ROY: Command,
Lieutenant is KIA.
We've lost our escort.
Request immediate support.
Over.
(GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOT)
- (CRASHING)
- (ROY GRUNTS)
(ROY PANTING)
(ROY GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
ROY: (ON RADIO) Command,
the Lieutenant's body
can be recovered...
just outside Walther crater.
Sorry for the loss.
Over.
COMMAND PERSONNEL:
Roger that, Major.
Uh, Colonel Pruitt,
we're picking up
an irregular heartbeat
through your system.
We suggest you get that
checked out immediately.
ROY: He's supposed to be
my security blanket.
I'm fine.
ROY: Why does he still do it?
Why can't he just let go?
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
My dad couldn't either.
ROMANO: Major,
we've been expecting you.
If you have any personal
business you need to tend to,
I suggest doing it now.
Your rocket
will leave momentarily.
PRUITT: Stand down, Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
Roy, just let me sit down.
- (SIGHS WEARILY)
- Colonel, what is it?
I'm not going to be able
to go with you to Mars.
But there are things
you need to know, Roy.
Every minute counts.
ANNOUNCER: (ON PA)
Cepheus crew,
prepare for pre-launch checks.
SPACECOM communicated with me.
It is classified.
Take it.
It will put you
at great risk.
They do not trust you
on SPACECOM.
But it is crucial...
(PRUITT GROANING)
Sergeant!
ANNOUNCER:
Commencing pre-launch checks.
You have to go, Roy. Go.
Go!
ROY: Captain, Major McBride,
com check.
TANNER: (ON RADIO)
Loud and clear, sir.
Welcome aboard the Cepheus.
ROY: I'll be hitching a ride
with you if that's all right.
TANNER: Yes,
we were alerted, sir.
On our way to Mars,
the very last stop.
We had two joining us?
It'll just be one,
I'm afraid.
Well, we still like you,
Major... McBride!
I think we might
just have ourselves
the son of a legend
onboard with us, team.
Roy, son of Clifford McBride.
Oh, wow!
TANNER: How 'bout that?
Best in the galaxy.
Welcome aboard, sir.
ROY: They are scientists
and technicians...
long haulers.
Captain, could you
contact Control, and ask
about the condition
of a Colonel Pruitt?
Sure, will do now, sir.
SPACECOM,
could we get a status...
ROY: They seem at ease
with themselves.
What must that be like?
Major, the Colonel was taken
for emergency surgery.
- Copy.
- TANNER: Check list complete.
ROY: They're oblivious
to my purpose.
TANNER: Destination,
Ersa Research Station, Mars.
The last manned outpost
in our solar system.
Duration 19 days,
14 hours and 33 minutes. Over.
Dear Saint Christopher,
protect me today
in all my travels
along the road's way.
Give me your warning sign
if danger is near.
So that I may stop...
TANNER: Perfect,
cue the minibar.
Command, we're gonna give out
the mood stabilizers now.
Our psych evals to follow.
Frank.
TANNER: 'Cause Lord knows
SPACECOM wouldn't want you...
getting all emotional
on us up here, again.
(MOCK CRYING)
STANFORD: Deavers.
Major?
TANNER: Get me one of those,
candy man.
STANFORD: Captain.
(OLD JAZZ MUSIC
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Captain, I have a small
oxygen leak in my suit.
I'm just gonna
check my patch.
TANNER: Have fun back there.
We'll let you know
if we spot any ETs.
(CLICKS BUTTON)
Hello, SPACECOM.
We're out here, Cepheus responding.
Smooth sailing.
OPERATOR: (ON RADIO)
Roger, Cepheus,
we have your telemetry.
TANNER: Boys and girls,
time for some Cidofovir.
A schmear a day
keeps the hair away.
(LAUGHING)
FRANKLIN: Nice, Deavers, nice.
STANFORD: Back me up,
I've never touched the stuff.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: (ON SPEAKERS)
This is an urgent update
for Colonel Pruitt,
Thomas F...
regarding the status
of the Lima Project.
SPACECOM believes
it has detected
a possible SOS signal...
from the crew
of the Lima Project.
The message could indicate
that Commander H.
Clifford McBride...
intentionally disabled
all external communications.
Under such circumstances...
the Commander may
have lost all control.
If this is the case...
and communication
cannot be made
through his son on Mars...
then all other efforts
must be undertaken
to destroy the Commander...
and halt the surges.
This message is top secret.
ROY: What happened
to my dad?
What did he find out there?
Did it break him?
Or was he always broken?
My father...
the most decorated astronaut
in the history of the program.
U.S. Air Force Academy...
his doctorate at MIT.
He promised me that one day
I could join him
in his pursuits...
that he'd come back for me.
And I believed him.
First man to Jupiter.
First to Saturn.
And then... nothing.
(ALARM BEEPING)
TANNER: Commence slow down,
booster three.
We're slowing down.
TANNER: Yes, sir.
Got a mayday
from another craft, sir.
Captain,
this is a classified mission,
we cannot stop.
Our destination is Mars.
Ersa Station.
TANNER: Major,
this is a mayday.
Stopping is protocol.
Any supply craft
can answer that call.
The mission
is the priority, Captain.
Do you not hear
what I'm saying?
Major, with respect, as I say,
we are obligated to stop.
As you're merely a passenger,
I'm not sure
I comprehend your position.
'Course, you are
well within your rights
to take command
of this craft...
but if so, you will have to
reveal your objectives.
Attend to the mayday.
TANNER: Command, craft
is registered as Norwegian.
The Vesta IX,
orbiting asteroid Toro...
registered for
biomedical research...
- on Comet 17-P, Holmes.
- RESPONDER: (ON RADIO) Copy.
TANNER: Vesta IX,
we're responding
to your distress call.
Do you read?
The distress call
is fairly recent.
Maybe they were hit
by The Surge.
Command, possible forced entry
to the Vesta required.
Either
First Lieutenant Stanford
or I will take
a little spacewalk...
and make our way
to the craft, over.
RESPONDER: Yes, sir.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Donald, what are you thinking?
Wanna go out there?
Uh, yeah.
Doesn't matter to me.
ROY: He's scared.
TANNER: Yeah, I know,
my suit smells
like a locker room, too.
Oh, hell, I could use
a good stretch anyway.
ROY: Most of us spend
our entire lives in hiding.
I'll accompany you, Captain.
TANNER: Very good.
STANFORD: (ON RADIO)
Vesta lists 26 souls onboard.
Craft registered
for biomedical
and animal research.
TANNER: Sorry about
that little tiff
back there, Major.
I'm honored
to be out here with ya.
You know, your dad
is the reason why
a lot of us are doing
what we're doing.
He went farther
than anybody.
He was the best of us.
Imagine the things he saw.
Imagine.
Vesta , this is Cepheus
responding
to your mayday signal.
Do you read?
Cepheus, the craft
is not responding.
Forced entry required.
I am now initiating
mayday entry code.
ROY: Vesta , this is Cepheus
responding to your mayday.
Do you read?
TANNER: Major,
I'll take Truss 5.
Why don't you start
with Truss 2?
Don't wander off
too far, now.
Where is everybody?
ROY: Vesta , this is Cepheus
responding to your mayday.
Do you read?
Tanner, McBride, check.
Tanner, do you copy?
Tanner?
(SCREECHING)
(ROY GRUNTING)
STANFORD: (ON RADIO) Repeat,
calling for Major McBride.
Calling for Captain Tanner.
(SCREECHING)
(PRIMATE SCREECHING)
(PANTING)
ROY: Stay calm. I got you.
Make it back.
(CLATTERING)
Cepheus, Captain was attacked
by a research primate.
Emergency medical stand by.
Attempting extraction now.
(ALARM BLARING)
(ROY GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(STRAINING)
(AUTOMATED VOICE
SPEAKING NORWEGIAN)
SPACECOM PERSONNEL: (ON RADIO)
Cepheus, this is SPACECOM.
Real sorry about that setback.
First Lieutenant Stanford is
in command of the craft...
until Captain Tanner
can resume his duties. Over.
STANFORD: SPACECOM, this is
First Lieutenant Stanford.
Captain Tanner is dead.
We take comfort knowing that
the Captain embraced
the rewards...
FRANKLIN: May the angels and
the saints come to meet you,
as you go forth
from this life.
May you meet your Redeemer
face to face,
and enjoy the vision
of God forever.
Amen.
AUTOMATED VOICE: (ON SPEAKERS)
McBride, Roy R.
Are you ready for your
psychological evaluation?
ROY: Yes.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Please begin.
ROY: I am on my way
to Mars.
We answered
a mayday call, and...
ended in tragedy.
We lost the Captain.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Your answer
is being processed.
Please continue.
Well, that's it.
I mean, we...
We go to work,
we do our jobs...
and then it's over.
We're here,
and then we're gone.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Please describe
how the incident itself
affected you.
The attack...
it was full of rage.
I understand that rage.
I've seen that rage
in my father...
and I've seen
that rage in me.
Because I'm angry...
that he took off.
He left us.
You know...
but when I look
at that anger,
if I push it aside
and just put it away...
all I see is hurt.
I just see pain.
I think it keeps me
walled off...
walled off
from relationships...
and opening myself up and,
you know,
really caring for someone.
And I don't know
how to get past that.
I don't know how
to get around that.
And it worries me.
And I don't wanna be that guy.
I don't wanna be my dad.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Your psychological evaluation
has been approved.
If you wish to obtain
a complete...
STANFORD: Major,
would you commence
auto-landing sequence?
ROY: Copy.
STANFORD: SPACECOM,
we're approaching Mars.
Ersa Station, south. Over.
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
What the hell was that?
DEAVERS:
Is that another surge?
STANFORD: I think we just lost
primary electrical bus.
ROY: Switching to bus Charlie.
Captain, we're coming in
too hot.
Our angle's off 20 degrees.
STANFORD: I...
(ALARM BEEPING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: Warning.
Incorrect angle of descent.
ROY: Go to manual.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Warning.
Incorrect angle of descent.
- Warning.
- ROY: Go to manual.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Incorrect angle of descent.
FRANKLIN: Captain,
you need to do something.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Incorrect angle of descent.
STANFORD: I think I'm, uh...
ROY: Go to manual.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Danger.
- Danger.
- Initiating manual override.
Item 3-2...
On my mark, execute.
Mark. I have command
of the ship.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Danger.
Danger.
ROY: 2,000 meters.
1,000 meters.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Warning.
Incorrect angle of descent.
Four...
three...
two...
one.
Contact.
Engine shut down.
Engine saved.
Your ship, Captain.
Major, would you, uh, start
post-landing sequence, please?
Copy that.
Captain, I believe you
understand why I did that.
I will not report it
to SPACECOM.
PERSONNEL: (ON SPEAKERS)
This is an emergency alert.
We have experienced
an external power surge.
However,
all underground systems
remain fully operational.
And there is no reason
for panic.
ROY: My destination.
PERSONNEL: We repeat,
all underground systems
are fully operational.
ROY: Seven weeks since Earth,
since air, since sun.
TANYA: Hey, earthlings!
Welcome
to Ersa Research Station.
- ROY: Trees and birds.
- TANYA: I'm glad you made it.
DEAVERS: Thank you.
I need your logs please.
Thank you.
STAFF: Sir?
TANYA: You got hit
by another surge, huh?
Thank God we're underground,
but the next one
could be the big one.
I mean, it has been crazy
around here.
ROY: This was my dad's
last known stop.
TANYA: Everyone's been
running around
like it's all gonna
end tomorrow.
Sir, you can step over here.
Put your palm down there.
Very good. Thank you.
All right, you guys are good
to move to the next concourse.
The Director will meet you.
Thank you.
HELEN: Welcome
to the red planet, Major.
I'm Helen Lantos,
Director of Operations here.
Nice to see a new face
for a change.
Follow me.
You should be glad
you arrived safely.
We had some kind of
cosmic storm.
We lost three astronauts
trying to land.
No one knows
what's causing them.
- Major?
- ROY: Yes?
CHIP: We're glad
you made it.
Thanks, Helen,
we can take it from here.
You're not authorized
at this level.
Major?
Well, thank you.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Stand by
for secure laser transmission.
Attempting top secret link.
Range: Neptune.
"This is Major Roy McBride.
"I'm communicating through
a secure laser transmission...
"sent from
the communications hub
"on Ersa Base,
North America sector, Mars.
"I'm attempting to reach
Doctor Clifford McBride.
"This is
Doctor McBride's son, Roy.
"Father, if you can hear me...
"I'm attempting
to communicate with you.
"SPACECOM wants you to know
"that they are aware
of the disturbances...
"and that it cannot be
your responsibility.
"They would like
all information...
"about attempts
that you are making
"to ameliorate the situation.
"They would also like
to tell you...
"they're willing to help
and provide
"for a rescue mission
if possible.
"I hope you receive
this message.
"Over and out."
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Transmission sent.
Awaiting response.
CHIP: Roy,
we'll try again next cycle.
(WINGS FLUTTERING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
ROY: They're using me.
Goddamn them.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
I don't know
if I hope to find him...
or finally be free of him.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Dad...
(MOUTHING)
Dad, I'd like
to see you again.
I recall how we used to watch
black and white
movies together...
and musicals
were your favorite.
I remember you tutoring me
in math.
You instilled in me
a strong work ethic.
"Work hard, play later,"
as you said.
You should know
I've chosen a career
that you would approve of.
I've dedicated my life
to the exploration of space.
And I thank you for that.
So, I hope we can reconnect.
Your loving son, Roy.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Transmission sent,
awaiting response.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Thank you so much, Major,
for all your help.
We'll be returning you
to the Earth
in short order.
Thank you.
Excuse me. Did you get a
response from my father?
Major,
your personal connection
has made you unsuited...
for continued service
on this mission.
ROY: He answered me,
didn't he?
Major, we will let you know
any details
as soon as possible.
CHIP: Roy.
Your pulse is very fast.
I know!
There's also some issues
with your biorhythms.
Those will need
to be addressed
before you can
safely return to Earth.
Would you please
follow that man
to take
a psychological evaluation?
Major.
Captain.
Captain!
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
AUTOMATED VOICE: McBride, Roy R.
Are you ready
for your
psychological evaluation?
Yes.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
How are you feeling
in your current state?
Good, thank you.
I will be returning
to Earth soon.
I'm content
to go home, and...
AUTOMATED VOICE:
You have failed
your psychological evaluation.
You will be returned
to a comfort room
until you are deemed...
Contact U.S. SPACECOM.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Provide
contact and priority code.
Request emergency
communication
with General Stroud.
Priority code,
Zulu-5-5-Bravo-Papa.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Your priority
code is no longer valid.
Please contact
a representative
if this restriction
is an error.
(LOUD THUD)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
You're going back
to Earth now?
Can I help you?
I've only been there once.
As a child.
I was born here.
But I remember it so well.
It was... beautiful.
Ma'am, I'd really appreciate
my privacy right now.
You're here because of
the cosmic rays, aren't you?
That's classified.
The craft you came in,
the Cepheus...
they want me to requisition
it for deep space...
with nuclear munitions
onboard.
Did you know that?
It's for a search
and destroy mission.
I am responsible for more
than 1,100 people here.
On this base.
Now, I need to know.
Are we gonna die?
I don't know
what happens now.
I know who you are.
You are
Clifford McBride's son.
Yes.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, then we're both victims
of the Lima Project.
My parents left
for that expedition.
You and I share
a great loss, Roy.
Please, just tell me.
The Cepheus leaves
in five hours.
ROY: You were right.
The Surge is coming
from the Lima Project.
Ultimate catastrophe
is very possible.
SPACECOM has determined
that I am unfit to carry on.
That's all I know.
I believe
your father is alive.
They never told you what
happened to him out there,
did they?
AUTOMATED VOICE:
U.S. Space Command
Top Secret Briefing.
Alpha-Papa-4-2-7-8.
Communications has received
the following mayday call...
from the crew
of the Lima Project,
under the command
of H. Clifford McBride.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
This is Clifford McBride,
reporting from
the Lima Project.
I'm disclosing a tragedy.
Here, on the edge
of our solar system,
some of our people...
have been unable to handle
the psychological distress...
of being so far away
from home.
They desired
to return to Earth,
and I could not permit that.
And I have to report
the reality
that they mutinied...
committed acts of sabotage
trying to commandeer my ship.
I was forced to react
with equal severity.
I disabled one section
of our station's
life support system...
and without doubt,
I did punish the innocent
along with the guilty.
We will not turn back.
We will venture further
into space.
We will find
alien intelligence.
I am forever driven
on this quest.
(SIGHS)
HELEN: SPACECOM
would never allow
their image to be shattered...
so they made him a hero
to protect themselves.
Your father
murdered my parents.
That monster
threatens us all.
And now it's your burden.
Can you get me
on that ship?
I can get you
to the rocket.
After that,
you're on your own.
I will deal with him.
I will deal
with my father.
HELEN: This is a map
of an underground lake
beneath the launchpad.
You'll be able to access
the ship from there.
We're approaching.
They're gonna come for you,
you know.
I know.
I don't care anymore.
I need to get back now,
do what I can.
Good luck.
(ROY PANTING)
ROY: I'm being pulled,
farther and farther
from the sun...
to you.
You're alive.
All this time.
I must accept the fact
I never really knew you.
Or am I you...
being pulled down
the same dark hole?
PERSONNEL: (ON SPEAKER) This
is Cepheus Launch Control...
at T-minus 11 minutes,
7 seconds and counting.
Our countdown continuing
and still aiming
toward a planned
lift-off time...
at 7:51, UTC.
This is Launch Control.
Launch is imminent.
(ROY GASPING)
(SPARKS CRACKLING)
(PANTING)
PERSONNEL: Final checks
from the flight azimuth
going on at this time...
and we're also synchronizing
the clocks
to the spacecraft...
with the Mission Control
Center in Ersa.
(PANTING)
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
The engines are armed.
Ten, nine...
eight, seven, six...
five, four...
We have commit.
...two, one.
(RUMBLING)
Lift-off.
We have lift-off.
7:51, UTC.
(ALARM BEEPING)
STANFORD: There's a breach.
DEAVERS:
It's the airlock breach.
STANFORD: SPACECOM,
this is Cepheus.
There's been a breach
in our airlock.
How to proceed? Over.
PERSONNEL: We see that, too.
We're checking it out.
Stand by.
STANFORD: SPACECOM,
we need orders, please. Over.
ROY: McBride
for Captain Stanford...
Do you read?
Jesus, it's McBride.
He's breached
the goddamn airlock.
Captain Stanford,
this is Major McBride.
I am onboard.
I am not a threat.
I repeat, I am not a threat.
STANFORD: Major, your presence
is jeopardizing the mission.
Stay where you are!
Do not proceed any further.
- SPACECOM...
- PERSONNEL: Stand by.
STANFORD: SPACECOM,
what are your orders?
PERSONNEL: We're determining
the course of action here.
STANFORD: We're about
to switch over
to long-range propulsion.
PERSONNEL:
Can you neutralize the threat?
You'll never make it
to Neptune without me.
You need me.
PERSONNEL:
Neutralize the Major.
By any means necessary,
you must neutralize the Major.
Copy that.
ROY: Don't listen to them,
Captain.
I will take
all accountability.
STANFORD: Major,
stay where you are.
Do not proceed any further.
Do you read? Over.
PERSONNEL: I say again,
neutralize the Major...
- by any means necessary.
- Yoshida, I am not a threat.
I am not the enemy.
I am on your side.
FRANKLIN: Major,
we have our orders.
Goddamn it! We're staging!
STANFORD: Frank,
get out of there! Deavers!
- Get back in your seat!
- ROY: Deavers, please!
(SCREAMING)
FRANKLIN: Son of a bitch!
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
(FIRE EXTINGUISHER HISSING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Air contaminated.
(COUGHING)
ROY: Get oxygen!
Yoshida, oxygen!
(STANFORD COUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Ventilator. Ventilator.
ROY: Breathe. (PANTING)
Breathe in!
ROY: What have I done?
Mission,
this is Major Roy McBride.
I boarded the Cepheus
against mission directives.
I did not do so
with hostile intent.
But because of my actions,
I regret to inform you...
all crew members
are now deceased.
The flight recorder
will tell the story.
History will have to decide.
I'm en route to Neptune.
I remain fully committed...
to the completion
of the mission...
namely to destroy
the Lima Project
in its entirety.
I'm switching off all comms.
I'm going dark until final
approach to avoid detection.
Over and out.
(ENGINES POWERING DOWN)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Estimated length of journey...
79 days, four hours,
eight minutes.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
EVE: (ON SPEAKERS)
You seem really preoccupied
with your work.
I just feel like I'm
on my own all the time.
I don't know
what we're doing.
You're so distant.
I mean, even when you're here,
I don't know where you are.
I feel like I'm looking
for you all the time...
trying to connect to you,
be close to you...
and it fucking sucks.
You know, I have my own life.
I'm my own person.
And I can't
just wait for you.
(WIND WHISTLING)
(CLICKS)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Feeding tube activated.
CLIFFORD: ...we have excited
real and enormous interest...
around the world,
and we're grateful for it.
See, we're doing big things
up here. Real big.
Namely, we are about to answer
the number one question...
when do we find
all the intelligent life
out there?
And we know we will,
according to
the Drake Equation.
(ENGINE POWERING DOWN)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
CLIFFORD: What you see here
is the new starshade,
just ready to deploy.
You see it opening up
just like a prairie flower
in the springtime.
But I think
you are no longer deserving...
so I guess...
this is goodbye.
Roy?
(LAUGHS)
CLIFFORD: ...retired from
the program leaves me to doubt
not only your judgement,
but your character.
See, we're just out
from Mars now.
EVE: He's been to Mars?
CLIFFORD: Just on our way
past Jupiter...
EVE: Do you wanna know
a secret?
CLIFFORD:
...eventually onto Neptune.
EVE:
♪ A, you're adorable
CLIFFORD: You have traded...
EVE:
♪ B, you're so beautiful
CLIFFORD: ...a glimpse
of the infinite...
EVE: ♪ C,
you're a cutie full of charms
♪ D, you're delightful
and E, you're exciting and
CLIFFORD: I am free
of your moral boundaries.
I have total clarity.
EVE: ♪ F,
you're a feather in my arms ♪
ROY: I am on my way
to Neptune...
CLIFFORD: Because we will find
our brothers and sisters...
ROY: The zero G
and the extended duration
of the journey
is affecting me...
both physically and mentally.
I am alone.
Something I always believed
I preferred.
I am alone.
But I confess...
it's wearing on me.
I am alone.
Over and out.
I've let so many people down.
EVE: (ON SPEAKERS) Hi, Roy.
Um...
I know
it's a little bit weird...
that I'm sending you
this video,
and not talking to you
in person...
I'm so selfish. I'm selfish.
I'm just so selfish.
I'm just a selfish person.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERS)
CLIFFORD: And I know for
certain I am doing God's work.
Forgiveness is bullshit.
CLIFFORD: We will find
our brothers and sisters...
Exaltation!
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Approaching location
determined by McBride, Roy R.
Retrieved, Mars secure
laser transmission.
(BEEPS)
Entering Neptune signal zone.
ROY: Execute 72 plus 99.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Executed.
Nuclear activation code
accessible
through system file 52B.
ROY: Flight recorder,
the Lima Project's orbit
is degrading.
Its position
has shifted somewhat
from the programmed
coordinates.
I will need
to take a transport capsule
to maneuver
around Neptune's rings.
The Cepheus will remain
in autopilot
while I complete the mission.
- (SWITCH CLICKS)
- (ENGINES POWERING UP)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
All my life, I was terrified
to confront him.
I'm terrified even now.
What do I expect?
In the end, the son suffers
the sins of the father.
- (ALARM BEEPING)
- (GRUNTS)
AUTOMATED VOICE: Warning.
Power surge. CPU damaged.
Warning. Power surge.
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
Lima, Major McBride
of the Cepheus.
United States Armed Forces,
Space Division.
Attempting to contact
Dr. Clifford McBride. Over.
Lima, Cepheus.
Do you read? Over.
(SOFT RUMBLING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Craft damaged. Unable to dock.
(CRANKS)
(CLASSIC POP MUSIC
PLAYING FAINTLY ON SPEAKERS)
(MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
(STATIC FEEDBACK)
- CLIFFORD: Roy?
- (GASPS SOFTLY)
Roy, is that you?
I have cataracts,
I don't see very well.
Hi, Dad.
You alone?
Oh, yeah.
Captain always goes down
with the ship.
(CHUCKLES)
I've been here
quite a while alone.
I'm trying to stop
this goddamn surge.
What happened?
My last loyal few
tried to escape.
And they started all this.
They caused a meltdown
out there, Roy.
We fought, and our struggle
caused catastrophe.
It's why I'm here.
I'm gonna stop it.
Get the two of us
back home, maybe.
Home?
Yep.
This is home.
This is a one-way voyage,
my son.
You're talking about Earth?
There was never anything
for me there.
I never cared about you,
or your mother...
or any of your small ideas.
For 30 years...
I've been breathing this air,
eating this food...
enduring these hardships...
and I never once thought
about home.
I know, Dad.
I knew this would
widow your mother...
and orphan you...
but I found my destiny.
So, I abandoned my son.
I still love you, Dad.
I'm taking you back.
Hmm... I have work to do.
I have infinite work to do.
I must find intelligent life.
It's time to go.
We don't have much time.
Come on.
I admire your courage
for coming alone, Roy...
traveling all this way...
following me here.
Makes me wonder what we could
have accomplished together.
But I guess...
the fates have deprived me
of the partner
I should have had.
If we'd had more people
like you...
we could have pressed on,
could've found
what we're looking for.
My crew examined
all the data...
discovered no other life
out there.
No other consciousness.
They quit.
(CLIFFORD SIGHS)
Sometimes...
the human will must overcome
the impossible.
You and I have to
continue on, Roy. Together.
To find what science claims
does not exist.
You and I, together, Roy.
Because the Lima Project
has told us...
that we're all alone
in the knowable universe.
I can't fail.
You can't let me fail, Roy.
Dad...
you haven't.
Now, we know...
we're all we've got.
(SWITCH CLICKS)
AUTOMATED VOICE: Armed.
T-minus three hours.
(ROY GROANS)
(GRUNTING) Dad! Stop!
(GRUNTING)
Roy!
Let me go.
(GRUNTING)
Let me go, Roy.
Roy, let me go.
Dad!
Let me go, Roy.
Unhook me.
Unhook me, son.
(ROY PANTING)
(ROY SCREAMS)
(INAUDIBLE)
ROY: Why go on?
Why keep trying?
CLIFFORD: You're gathering
my work, I see.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Data download initiated.
We're a dying breed, Roy.
ROY: He captured
strange and distant worlds
in greater detail
than ever before.
They were beautiful,
magnificent...
full of awe and wonder.
But beneath
their sublime surfaces...
there was nothing.
No love or hate.
No light or dark.
He could only see
what was not there...
and missed what was
right in front of him.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
Command,
this is Major Roy McBride.
I made it
to the Lima Project.
I am destroying
the structure...
to prevent any further surges
from reaching Earth...
using the nuclear munitions
onboard.
I will attempt to return
using the explosion
as my primary propellant.
In the case
I do not survive,
I've retrieved significant
data from the Lima.
And all efforts should be made
to retrieve my craft.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Trajectory, Earth.
2.714 billion miles.
I am looking forward to
the day my solitude ends.
And I'm home.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Detonation
in T-minus 20 seconds.
(RUMBLING)
MAN 1:
The aboard advisory system.
MAN 2: Affirmative,
we're ready.
MAN 1: USP flight system
is operational.
Thank you.
MAN 2: K-R-5 on the 4-2.
MAN 1: Good copy, flight.
We're ready to go.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)
(THUDS)
(ENGINE POWERS DOWN)
MAN: Coming in, clean.
Copy that. Thanks.
One ready to go.
Data is good.
We have all good. All good.
You're all right, Major.
ROY: I'm steady, calm.
I slept well. No bad dreams.
I am active and engaged.
I'm aware of my surroundings
and those
in my immediate sphere.
I'm attentive.
I'm focused
on the essential...
to the exclusion
of all else.
I'm unsure of the future...
but I'm not concerned.
I will rely
on those closest to me.
And I will share
their burdens...
as they share mine.
I will live...
and love.
Submit.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org